

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Recent graduate in computer science with strong mathematical skills and software engineering emphasis, interested in everything from AI to fullstack development. Previous experience includes a deep background in humanities and languages with international teaching experience.

#### **SKILLS**

- Software Engineering
- Fullstack Engineering
- Mathematics

- Natural Languages
- Project Management
- Al/ML

- Audio Engineering
- Databases

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Graduate Student Teaching Assistant

March 2020 - June 2020

- Portland State University | Portand, OR
  Helped students with coursework in Frontend Web Technologies course.
- Graded assignments for Discrete Math course.

Teacher May 2010 - August 2016

#### Various

- Summer 2016: Taught ESL to high school students from Spain.
- 9/15-6/16: Taught Chinese and second grade using Connections Academy.
- Spring 2015: Taught ESL to various ages in Itoshima, Japan
- Fall/Winter 2014: Taught ESL to various ages in Chongqing, China
- 5/10-6/11: Taught ESL to kindergarten kids in Beijing, China.

Teahouse Personnel

October 2007 - June 2018

Brew Dr. Tea | Portland, OR

• Various roles: barista, delivery driver, warehouse management.

#### **EDUCATION**

Master's Computer Science (3.95 GPA)

June 2020

Portland State University, Portland, OR

Accelerated Undergraduate Computer Science

2019

Portland State University, Portland, OR

Audio Engineering 2018

Portland Community College, Portland, OR

Post-Bacc Inquiry: World History, Politics, Economics, German, etc. Portland State University, Portland, OR	2015
Mandarin Chinese HSK 5 and Advanced Oral HSK	2014
Confucius Institute, Portland, OR	2014
Bachelor of Arts English Literature	2009
Portland State University, Portland, OR	

## **LANGUAGES**

English, Chinese, Spanish

# **PROGRAMMING**

C, C++, Java, Android, Python, Javascript, React, Haskell, SQL

# **PROJECTS**

Portfolio: https://charboltron.github.io

### **LINKS**

Github: https://www.github/charboltron

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/charles-b-0723051b0/